Hi... Danny?
你好... Danny?
Hi Nancy. Hi. How are you?
你好, Nancy. 你好. 你好吗?
Fine, thanks. Nice tuxedo.
很好, 谢谢. 礼服不错.
I'm... I'm... I'm going to a wedding.
我, 我, 我要去参加一个婚礼.
For a minute there, you looked like one of those balloon-delivery guys.
有那么一分钟, 你看上去像个送气球的.
The balloons are for the wedding.
这气球是为婚礼准备的.
Oh.
The couple is Danish, and the Danes have an old custom.
这对新婚夫妇是丹麦人, 丹麦人有一个古老的风俗.
Actually, it's not that old, but the balloons are part of it.
事实上, 并没有那么古老, 但气球是其中的一部分.
Part of the wedding.
是婚礼的一部分.
Yes.
是的.
Everybody has something.
每个国家的人都有自己的传统.
Americans throw birdseed.
美国人扔鸟食.
The Japanese have rubber cakes.
日本人有橡皮蛋糕.
In Liechtenstein, they kidnap the bride from the reception.
在Liechtenstein, 人们把新娘从喜宴上抢走.
... Or is that the Zimbabweans?
...或者那是Zimbabwean人的习俗吧?
You know, Nancy, I was just on my way out.
You know, Nancy, 我正要外出.
Of course. Don't let me keep you.
当然. 别因为我而耽搁了.
You don't want to be late for a wedding, especially if you're in the bridal party.
你当然不想参加婚礼迟到, 尤其如果你是新娘家的客人的话.
Are you the best man?
你是伴郎吗?
No. Yes. Sort of. Nice talking to you. Bye.
不是. 是的. 算是吧. 很高兴和你聊天. 再见.